Hispanic Women's Network of Texas Records
Nettie Lee Benson Latin American Collection
- Part 1: Original Collection
  - Local Chapters, 1988-2004
    - Austin Chapter, 1988-2004 (Box 29)
      - Various Binders (Box 33)
        Materials collected and grouped together (usually in three-ring binders) by Austin Chapter members. Included items may be from the Austin Chapter or from the statewide organization. They are listed in roughly chronological order.
        - President's Binder, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Secretary Binder, Austin Subcommittees and BOD Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - BOD and Austin Chapter Minutes, General Binder, 1989-1994 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - President's Binder, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - President's Binder, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - President's Binder, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2-12)
        - Roster, Agendas, Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Austin Chapter Binder, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 2-7)
        - Austin Chapter Notebook, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - BOD Representative Folder, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - Various, 1992-2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Photographs, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Dallas Chapter, 1990-2003 (Box 36)
      - By-laws, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Chapter Reports, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee Meetings, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Executive Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - 1992 Convention Planning Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
      - Nominations Committee, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Meetings, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Meetings, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Meetings, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Meetings, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Events (Box 37)
        - Education Seminar Series, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
        - Education Seminar Series, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Education Seminar Series, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Retreat, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        - General, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - General, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - General, 2000-2003 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters (Box 37)
        - 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - 1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - 1994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - 1998 (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - 2000 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Various (Box 37)
        - Membership, 1988-1993 (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - Photo Album, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Corpus Christi Chapter, 1991-2003 (Box 38)
      - General, 1991-1997 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - General, 2000-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Scrapbook, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - El Paso Chapter, 1989-1997 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Fort Worth Chapter (Box 38)
      - Chapter Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Events, 1991; 1997 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Lower Rio Grande Chapter, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Lubbock Chapter, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - McAllen Chapter, 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - San Antonio Chapter, 1993-2003 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1988-2001
    - Conference photographs, 1999 October (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
    - Artifacts (name badge with pins and 1999 pocket calendar) (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - VHS tape, "Hispanic Women in Texas," Channel 8 Newscast of 1st State Conference, 1988 (Box 37)
  - Oversized Material, 1995; 2001 (Box 80)
    - White House Proclamation of National Hispanic Heritage Month, 1995 (Box 80)
    - Corpus Christi Proclamation of Hispanic Women's Network Day, 1995 October 21 (Box 80)
    - Poster for 3rd Annual Cesar Chavez Birthday Celebration, Austin, 2001 March 31 (Box 80)
    - Conference posters, 1987; 1988 (Map case OV, Folder 1)
- Part 2: Additions
  Part 2 of this collection consists of material donated between 2005-2018.
  - General and Administrative, 1988-2012
    - Executive Material, 1991-2012 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
    - Executive Material, 1991-2012 (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Agendas and Meeting Minutes, 2004-2012 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Executive Officers' Rules and Regulations, 1999-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Standing Rules and By-laws, 1996-2006 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2011 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Forms, 1993-2000 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1988-2006 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Directories, 1991-1996 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Directories, 1998-2002 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Directories, 2003-2005 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, 1993-2014
    - Financial Materials, 1993-2014
      - Check Requests, 1999-2005 (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
      - Expense and Treasurer Reports, 1993-2014 (Box 43, Folder 1-5)
      - Expense and Treasurer Reports, 1993-2014 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
      - Grants, 2004-2007 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Receipts, 1994-2009 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
      - Receipts, 1994-2009 (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
      - Treasurer Materials, 2001-2013 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1993-2014 (Box 45)
      - 1993 July (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - 1994 January (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - 1994 April (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - 1996 January (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - 1996 July (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - 1998 October (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - 1999 January (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - 1999 April (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - 1999 July (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - 1999 October (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - 2000 January (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - 2000 April (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - 2000 July (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - 2000 October (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - 2000 December (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - 2001 January (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - 2001 April (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - 2001 July (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - 2001 August (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - 2001 October (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - 2002 January (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - 2002 April (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - 2002 June (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - 2002 July (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - 2002 October (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - 2003 January (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - 2003 April (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - 2003 July (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - 2003 September (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - 2003 October (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - 2003 November (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - 2004 January (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - 2004 April (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - 2004 June (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - 2004 August (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - 2004 October (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - 2005 January (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - 2005 April (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - 2005 July (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - 2005 April (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - 2005 October (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - 2005 November (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - 2006 January (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - 2006 April (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - 2006 July (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - 2006 September (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - 2006 November (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - 2007 January (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - 2007 April (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - 2007 July (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - 2007 October (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - 2008 February (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - 2008 April (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - 2008 August (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - 2008 October (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - 2009 April (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - 2010 January (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - 2010 April (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - 2010 July (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - 2010 October (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - 2011 April (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - 2011 July (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - 2012 July (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - 2012 October (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - 2013 January (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - 2013 April (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - 2013 July (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - 2013 October (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - 2014 January (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - 2014 April (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - 2014 May (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - 2014 July (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - 2014 October (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Committees, 1993-2015
    - Communication Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee, 1997-2013 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, 1995-2008 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Membership Committee, 1993-2015 (Box 48, Folder 4-6)
    - Newsletter Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1998-2003 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Steering Committee, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Technology Committee, 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Events, 1989-2014 (Box 49)
    - Conferences, 1989-2014 (Box 49)
      - Annual Conference, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Annual Conference, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Annual Conference, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Annual Conference, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Annual Conference Photographs, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Annual Conference, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Annual Conference, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Annual Conference, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Annual Conference, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Annual Conference, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 13-14)
      - Annual Conference Photographs, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Annual Conference, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Annual Conference Photo Album, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Annual Conference, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Annual Conference, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 2-6)
      - Annual Conference, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
      - Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
      - Annual Conference, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Annual Conference, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
      - Annual Conference, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
      - Annual Conference, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
      - Annual Conference, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Annual Conference, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Annual Conference, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Annual Conference, 2010 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Annual Conference, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Annual Conference, 2012 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Annual Conference, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Annual Conference, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Events, 1993-2007 (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous Events, 1993-2007 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - State Board Retreat, 2003 January (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Diabetes Walk, 2003 October (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Scholarship Awards, 2003 May (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Las Estrellas, 2003 October (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Reception, Ballet Folkórico, 1993 March 30 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Corpus Christi Reception, 1995 October 20 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Dallas Luncheon, 1995 January 21 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Miss Senior America, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Valentine's Day, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Austin Luncheon, 1995 April 29-30 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Redeveloping HWNT's Mission - Austin, Texas, 1994 January 15 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Women's Hall of Fame Reception - Austin, Texas, 1994 January 29 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Collected Material, 2001-2016 (Box 54)
    - Collected Material, 2001-2016 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Collected Material, 2001-2016 (Box 55, Folder 1-4)
    - Collected Material, 2001-2016 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Proclamations and Decrees, 2005-2006 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Local Chapters, 1981-2014 (Box 56)
    - Austin Chapter, 1992-2011 (Box 56)
      - Clippings, 2002-2011 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Donations and Sponsors, 2004-2006 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Events, 1992-2009 (Box 56)
        - Cesar Chavez Day, 2001-2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - Dia de las Madres, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - Día de los Niños, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Longhorn Leader Day, 2001-2004 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Silent Auction, 2002-2009 (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous Events, 1992-2004 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Executive Material, 1999-2005 (Box 57)
        - Board Leadership, 1999-2005 (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Meeting Notes and Agendas, 1999-2005 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
        - Chapter Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Financial Material, 1998-2004 (Box 57)
        - Check Requests and Receipts, 1998-2004 (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Check Requests and Receipts, 1998-2004 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
        - Expense Reports, 2000-2004 (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - Financial Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Membership, 1998-2008 (Box 59)
        - Membership, 1998-2008 (Box 59, Folder 2-5)
        - Membership, 1998-2008 (Box 60, Folder 1-5)
        - Membership, 1998-2008 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
      - Newsletter, 1998-2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1998-2010 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Scholarships, 1995-2004 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, 1990s (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Corpus Christi Chapter, 1997-2011 (Box 62)
      - Clippings, 2001-2011 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2010 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Donations and Sponsors, 1995-2010 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Certificates and Proclamations, 2010-2011 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Events, 1997-2013 (Box 62)
        - Las Estrellas, 1998-2013 (Box 62, Folder 6-8)
        - Locks of Love, 2007-2009 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Quinceñeara Fair Photographs, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Reception for Dr. Cleotilde Garcia Photographs, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 2001-2009 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous Events, 1997-2011 (Box 63, Folder 5-8)
      - Executive Material, 1996-2011
        - Meetings and Executive Material, 1996-2011 (Box 64, Folder 1-5)
        - Meetings and Executive Material, 1996-2011 (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
      - Financial Material (Box 65)
        - Financial Documents, 2000-2010 (Box 65, Folder 4-6)
        - Financial Documents, 2000-2010 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
      - Membership (Box 66)
        - Membership, 1995-2013 (Box 66, Folder 3-6)
        - Membership, 1995-2013 (Box 67, Folder 1-5)
      - Newsletters, 1998-2011 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
      - Reports, 1999-2014 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Photographs, 1990s-2000s (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Dallas Chapter, 1987-2014 (Box 68)
      - Clippings, 1993-2007 (Box 68, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Events, 1987-2003
        - Education Series, 1993-2003 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
        - Emerging Leaders Seminar, 1991-2002 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Empowering Latinas, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Noche de Gala, 1995-1998 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous Events, 1987-2003 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Executive Material, 1991-2004 (Box 70)
        - Meeting and Agendas, 1991-2004 (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
      - Financial Material, 1991-2007 (Box 70)
        - Financial Material, 1991-2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Membership, 1991-2007 (Box 70)
        - Membership, 1991-2007 (Box 70, Folder 4-6)
        - Membership, 1991-2007 (Box 71, Folder 1-5)
      - Newsletters, 1993-2004 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1991-2014 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Scholarships, 1993-1998 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Scrapbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Denton Chapter, 2009-2013 (Box 72)
      - Reports, 2009-2013 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - El Paso Chapter, 1999-2001 (Box 72)
      - Members, 1999-2001 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Fort Worth Chapter, 1987-2014 (Box 72)
      - Clippings, 1993-2009 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Events, 1987-2014 (Box 72)
        - Latinas in Progress, 2007-2011 (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
        - Miscellaneous Events, 1987-2009 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Executive Material, 1998-2011 (Box 72)
        - Meetings and Agendas, 1998-2011 (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
      - Financial Material, 1991-2008
        - Financial Material, 1991-2008 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Membership, 1987-2008 (Box 73, Folder 2-5)
      - Newsletters, 1999-2012 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1998-2014 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, 1994-2009 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Houston Chapter, 2009-2014 (Box 74)
      - Reports, 2009-2014 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Lower Rio Grande Valley Chapter, 2000-2013 (Box 74)
      - Clippings, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Membership, 2000-2007 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 2009-2013 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - McAllen Chapter, 2000-2013 (Box 74)
      - Clippings, 1996-2006 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Events, 1996-2007 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Membership, 2001-2006 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - San Antonio Chapter, 1981-2014 (Box 74)
      - Clippings, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Events, 1981-2006 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Events, 1981-2006 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Meetings and Agendas, 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Membership, 1991-2011 (Box 75, Folder 3-6)
      - Newsletters, 1998-2008 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1999-2014 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Audiovisual Material, 1994-2015 (Box 75)
    - Unlabeled Photographs, 2003-2015 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Floppy Disks, 1994-2004 (Box 76)
      - HWNT, 1994-1997
      - HWNT, 1998-1999
      - HWNT Conference Registration Form/Barbie Tasks/HWNT 2000 Conference/HWNT 2001 Conference, 1999-2001
      - HWNT, 2000
      - Letterhead/Blank Letterhead/Membership Form/Meeting Sites 2000
      - HWNT Josie/Roster/Attendance/Agenda/Letter/Minutes, 2001 January
      - HWNT Conference 2001/Letters fo McAllen's Merchants
      - HWNT Treasurer's Manual, 2001
      - HWNT 2001 State Roster and Minutes
      - October Roster/January 2002/Agenda, 2001-2002
      - HWNT Membership, 2001
      - HWNT Minutes/Agendas/Roster/State Board Meetings, 2002 March
      - HWNT Newsletter, 2002 March 21
      - Garage Sale HWNT/Volunteer Letterhead, 2003
      - Dia de las Madres, 2003
      - HWNT Bank Recon Reports/Scholarships, 2003
      - HWNT Letterhead/Invoices/Misc. Forms (IRS), 2003
      - Tax Name/Tax Letter Copies, 1994-1997
      - HWNT Miscellaneous Forms, undated
      - HWNT Scholarship Criteria, undated
      - HWNT Logo, undated
      - HWNT Working Desk, undated
      - HWNT 2nd Mail Out, undated
      - HWNT July Board Meeting/Panelist Letters 1-4/Attorney's Letter, undated
      - Attorney's List, undated
      - Example of Recon Report, undated
    - DAT Tapes, 2000s
      - 2002 October
      - Untitled, undated
  - Scrapbooks, 1998-2009
    - Austin Scrapbook, 1998-2000 (Box 77)
    - Austin Scrapbook, 2001-2003 (Box 77)
    - Corpus Christi Scrapbook, 1998 (Box 78)
    - Corpus Christi Scrapbook, 1999
    - Fort Worth Chapter Scrapbook, 2007-2008 (Box 79)
    - Fort Worth Scrapbook (1 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 80)
    - Fort Worth Scrapbook (2 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 80)
    - Latinas in Progress Scrapbook, 2007-2009 (Box 80)
  - Oversize Materials, 1990-2014
    - Fort Worth Chapter Banner, undated (Box 80)
    - Oversize Posters, 1990-2012 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Proclamations and Decrees (Box 80)
      - Corpus Christi, Texas Proclamation, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - National Hispanic Heritage Month Proclamation by the President of the United States (William J. Clinton), 1995 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Bexar County Proclamation, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - City of Houston Proclamation, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - State of Texas 21st Anniversary, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - City of San Antonio Proclamation, 2014 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Textiles, 1990s-2000s
    - Bags, 2005-2008 (Box 81-82)
    - T-Shirts, 2000s (Box 83)
      - Embracing the Infinite, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Mujer Hispana, Mujer de Hoy, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Austin Chapter, United States Census, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Hispanic Women's Network of Texas, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 4-6)
      - Fabulous Fort Worth Chapter, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Buttons and Pins, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Memorabilia, 1991-2007 (Box 83)
    - Rita Escamilla, Vice-Chair of Marketing, Plate Award, 2013-2014 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Linda Escamilla, The Appreciation, 2000s (Box 84)
    - Linda Escamilla, Founding Member of Austin Chapter, 2007 (Box 84)
    - HWNT 10th Annual Conference, Austin, Texas, 1996 October 18-20 (Box 84)
    - HWNT Vivan Las Hispanas 7th Annual Conference, 1993 October 8-10 (Box 84)
    - HWNT 9th Annual Conference, Corpus Christi, 1995 October 20-22 (Box 84)
    - 10th Annual Conference Koozie, 1996 October (Box 84)
    - HWNT Paper Weight, undated (Box 84)
    - HWNT, Remembering Our Past, Celebrating Our Future 6th Annual Conference, Dallas, 1992 October 15-18 (Box 85)
    - HWNT, Woman's Role, Effecting Change, 8th Annual Conference, San Antonio, 1994 October 14-16 (Box 85)
    - HWNT, Forging a New Leadership for the 21st Century, 5th Annual Conference, El Paso, 1991 October 10-13 (Box 85)
    - HWNT, 6th Annual Conference Paper Weight, 1992 October 15-18 (Box 85)
    - Key to the City of Fort Worth, undated (Box 85)
- Part 3: Additions
  Part 3 of this collection consists of material donated between 2019-2021.
  - General and Administrative, 1987-2005; undated (Box 86)
    - General and Administrative Files, 1987-1990 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
    - HWNT Annual Directories, 2000-2005 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Photograph headshot, labeled Irma and Terrie's, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, 2000-2019; undated
    - HWNT 2002-2003 State Board Binder No. 1 Board Meeting Minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - HWNT 2002-2003 State Board Binder No. 2 Financial Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - HWNT 2002-2003 State Board Binder No. 3 Committee Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - HWNT 2002-2003 State Board Binder No. 4 Chapter Reports, Annual Conference, 2001-2004 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - HWNT 2002-2003 State Board Binder No. 5 Bylaws, Standing Rules, Calendar of Events, 2001-2004 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - HWNT State Board of Directors Binder No.1 Meeting Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - HWNT State Board of Directors Binder No. 2 Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - McKay, Cecilia Binder, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2006; 2015 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2007-2017 (Box 88, Folder 3-5)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2007-2017 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2008-2016 (Box 89, Folder 2-3)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2010-2014 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2010-2016 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Morin, Guadalupe Files, 2013-2016 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - New Board Member Binder with By-laws and Schedule, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Meetings Binder, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
    - Reports, 2013; 2019 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Romero, Carla Secretary/Historian Binder, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 2-4)
    - Romero, Carla Files, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - State Board Retreats, 2019 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Trinidad, Dora Files, 2008-2010 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Committees, 2003; 2016,; undated
    - Membership Committee, 2003; undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Scholarship Committee, 2016 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Annual Conferences and Special Events, 1987-2019
    - Annual Conferences, 1988-2019
      - Annual Conference, 1988-1990 (Box 91, Folder 10-12)
      - 17th Annual Conference, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - 17th Annual Conference, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - 20th Annual Conference, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - 21st Annual Conference, 2007 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - 24th Annual Conference, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - 25th Annual Conference, 2011 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - 27th Annual Conference, 2013 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - 28th Annual Conference, 2014 (Box 92, Folder 7)